geojit.com 2014-06-25

# Best online share trading site, Equity Derivatives, Share broking company.

## 1. INTRODUCTION

We at Geojit BNP Paribas Financial Services Ltd and its affiliates (hereinafter referred to as ‘Geojit BNP Paribas’) are committed to protect our customers’ personal information and/or sensitive personal data and strive to maintain the privacy of your personal information. We have created this Privacy Policy to help you understand how we collect, use and protect your information when you visit our web and WAP sites and use our products and services. 

For the purpose of this Policy, “Personal information” is any information that relates to a natural person which, either by itself or can be used in combination with any other information available with Geojit BNP Paribas, for identifying such person. Sensitive personal data or information as defined under Rule 3 of IT (Reasonable security practices and procedures and sensitive personal data or information) Rules, 2011 has been considered as a part of personal information. 

## 2. COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Geojit BNP Paribas may collect and hold personal information relating to you and your identity that you have provided to us, such as on an application or Know Your Client (KYC) and member-client forms. We may also collect your personal information when you use our services or websites or otherwise interact with us during the course of our relationship. 

Personal information collected and held by us may include, amongst other things, your father’s name, spouse’s name, date of birth, residential and correspondence addresses (current and previous), telephone number, mobile phone number, email address, education and occupation related details and information contained in the documents used as proof of identity and proof of address and bank account. Geojit BNP Paribas collect, store, process Sensitive Personal Information, including password, financial information (details of annual income, networth, portfolio, Bank account, debit card, or other payment instrument details), depository details. We may also hold information related to your utilization of our services which may include your call details, your browsing history on our website and additional information provided by you while using our services any other information collected in relation to your use of our products and services ("information"). 

## 3. PURPOSE & USAGE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Geojit BNP Paribas does use your personal information for a variety of regulatory and business purposes. These include, but are not limited to: 

In case you do not provide your information or consent for usage of personal information or later on withdraw your consent for usage of the personal information so collected, Geojit BNP Paribas reserves the right to not provide the services or to withdraw the services for which, the said information was sought. 

## 4. DISCLOSURE AND TRANSFER OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

There may be certain circumstances, when Geojit BNP Paribas may be required to share the information given by you with the third parties. We may transfer your personal information or sensitive personal information collected, stored, processed by us to any other entity or organization located in India or outside India only in case it is necessary for providing services to you or for assisting in protecting the operation of Geojit BNP Paribas networks and systems or if you have consented (at the time of collection of information) to the same. 

We shall take all reasonable steps to ensure that the confidentiality of your information is maintained by imposing strict confidentiality standards on all the third parties with whom we part these information. In all circumstances we shall ensure that your personal information is protected by strict confidentiality agreement. We shall not allow any third parties to retain your personal information longer than what is warranted by the nature of services rendered. 

We will also impart your personal information wherever it is required to be disclosed under law to any of the governmental agency or regulatory bodies or court or any appropriate authority. 

## 5. SECURITY PRACTICES AND PROCEDURES

Geojit BNP Paribas adopt reasonable security practices and procedures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, or disclosure while it is under our control. Our security practices and procedures limit access to personal information on need-only basis. Further, our employees are bound by Internal Code of Conduct and Confidentiality Policies which obligate them to protect the confidentiality of personal information. 

We take adequate steps to ensure that our third parties adopt reasonable level of security practices and procedures to ensure security of personal information. We may retain your personal information for as long as required to provide you with services or if otherwise required under any law. 

Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this Website will be protected by encryption technology. You are also responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. 

We maintain the security of our internet connections however, for reasons outside of our control, security risks may still arise. Any personal information transmitted to us or from our online products or services will therefore be your own risk. However, we will strive to ensure the security of your information. We observe reasonable security measures to protect your personal information against hacking and virus dissemination. 

Please note that Geojit BNP Paribas website may contain links to third party links/websites over which we exercise no control. It is highly recommended that when you are accessing a non- Geojit BNP Paribas website, you should always read their privacy policy or website terms and conditions – especially if you are considering providing them with your personal information. 

## 6. GRIEVANCE REDRESSAL (ONLY PERSONAL INFORMATION RELATED AND NOT RELATED TO TRADING ACTIVITIES)

We are committed to safeguard your personal information collected and handled by us and look forward to your continued support for the same. In case of any feedback or concern regarding protection of your personal information, you can contact us at mathew_pv@geojit.com. Alternatively, you may also direct your privacy-related feedback or concerns to the Privacy Grievance Officer whose details are as mentioned below: 

  * **Name:** Mathew P.V
  * **Designation:** Territory Information Security Officer
  * **Details:**[mathew_pv@geojit.com](mailto:mathew_pv@geojit.com)
  * **Contact no:** 0484-2405501

## 7. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Geojit BNP Paribas reserves the right to amend or modify this Privacy Policy at any time, as and when the need arises. We request you to visit our website www.geojitbnpparibas.com periodically for contemporary information and changes.
